Path of Exile Gen 3 released a video
《流放之路》第三代发布了一段
called Runes of Al'Dur, Rune Crafting,
名为“奥杜尔的符文，符文制作”的视频，
where they're going to go over the
其中将详细介绍该
mechanic. So, let's watch it.
机制。 那么，我们一起来看吧。
&gt;&gt; All my life's work.
我毕生的心血。
The more I studied, the more I began to
我研究得越多，就越
see similar shapes in the stars above.
发现天上的星星形状相似。
It was then that I dedicated myself to
正是在那时，我立志
becoming
成为
a Rune Seeker.
一名符文探寻者。
&gt;&gt; Rune Seeker.
符文探寻者。
&gt;&gt; As Pharaoh so kindly explained, Runes
正如法老亲切地解释的那样，符文
are very powerful and ancient
是非常强大而古老的
inscriptions, and they can be socketed
铭文，可以镶嵌
into your items to grant them more
在你的物品上，赋予它们更大的
power.
力量。
During the league, inscribing symbols
在赛季期间，将符号刻印
into remnants will let you choose
在遗物上，可以让你
between a bunch of different crafting
在各种不同的制作
runes that you can use to enhance your
符文中进行选择，这些符文可以用来强化你的
items.
物品。
When you come across a remnant that has
当你遇到一个遗迹，其
a number of slots ranging from two
槽位数量从 2 个
to seven. The more slots, the more
到 7 个不等时。 槽位越多，
powerful the remnant encounter, but the
残余遭遇战的威力就越大，但
more options you'll have to choose
你也将面临更多的选择
between.
。
At the start of the game, you might find
游戏初期，你可能会发现
yourself crafting simple damage or
自己正在制作简单的伤害符文或
resistance runes.
抗性符文。
&gt;&gt; Okay, so this is at the beginning,
好的，这是在开头，
right? At the beginning of the campaign.
对吧？ 竞选之初。
Desert Rune will add fire damage, so
沙漠符文会增加火焰伤害，
that's if you need runes. That's cool.
如果你需要符文的话，可以选择它。 这很酷。   在
They rarely drop when we were in the
我们竞选期间，他们很少掉队
campaign. But, four blacksmith's
。 但是，在战役初期，拥有四块铁匠
whetstones would also be really nice
磨刀石也非常好，
early in the campaign, right? You get a
对吧？ 当你获得一件
solid weapon, you want those blacksmith
不错的武器时，你会想要那些铁匠
whetstones, cuz at that point you don't
磨刀石，因为那时你还没有
have access to the currency exchange.
办法进行货币兑换。
And then they also have bonus rewards.
此外，他们还有额外奖励。
That's cool. Hell yeah.
这很酷。 当然。
&gt;&gt; They're available at a lower level than
它们的价格比
you would normally be able to get them,
你通常能买到的价格要低，可以
giving you a decent power boost.
给你带来不错的实力提升。
But, things quickly get more
但是，事情很快变得更
interesting.
有趣了。
There are 22 runes for adding or
有 22 种符文可以用来添加或
modifying runic ward, a new resource
修改符文护盾，符文护盾是一种
that can protect you from death.
可以保护你免于死亡的新资源。
Using these runes, you can add an extra
使用这些符文，你可以增加一层额外的
defensive layer, or turn your runic ward
防御，或者将你的符文护盾
into an offensive weapon.
变成进攻性武器。
&gt;&gt; See, I don't like that.
你看，我不喜欢那样。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; This guy just This guy just survived
这家伙简直……这家伙就像
like his HP is at one. He got attacked
生命值只有1一样活了下来。 他遭到
twice, he should have died in those
两次攻击，本来应该死在那些攻击中。如果
Without runic ward, he dies. It looks
没有符文护符，他肯定会死。
like he could survive like a third
看起来他甚至能挺过第三次
attack, too. I feel like this is a
袭击。 我觉得
little bit too much hand-holding if it's
如果
this strong early in the campaign. Looks
竞选初期就这么强势，那就有点过度保护了。 看起来
really strong, is what I'm trying to
非常强劲，这就是我
say. If it makes the campaign a breeze,
想说的。 如果它让竞选变得轻而易举，
then it's going to be a problem for
那么
enjoyment in my opinion. There's got to
在我看来，这将会影响游戏的乐趣。
be a little bit of a challenge at least,
至少得有点挑战性，
some resistance, please.
有点阻力吧。
&gt;&gt; Pensive weapon, using Kelguran runic
沉思之器，运用凯尔古拉符文
skills.
技能。
There are also 13 runes that add powers
还有 13 种符文可以
specific to weapon types, like this one
为特定武器类型增加特殊能力，例如这种符文可以让
which gives a chance for grenades to
手榴弹有几率
explode a second time.
再次爆炸。
&gt;&gt; Ancient rune of
远古符文“
&gt;&gt; one which gives you a new buff called
一”，赋予你一个名为“
Druid
德鲁伊
&gt;&gt; Prowess is a stacking buff which grants
之力”的新增益效果，这是一个可叠加的增益效果，可使
10% increased skill speed and causes
技能速度提高 10%，并且使
hits with spell damage to grant three
法术伤害的攻击每层效果
range per stack for 10 seconds. Each
在 10 秒内增加 3 点射程。 每个
stack has an independent duration,
堆叠层数都有独立的持续时间，
maximum three stacks.
最多可堆叠三层。
&gt;&gt; The Prowess when heavy stunning enemies.
重击敌人时的强大能力。
In addition, there are 22 runes designed
此外，还有 22 种符文旨在让
to give you power at low levels, like
你在低等级时获得力量，例如
this one which gives you a bunch of
这种符文可以给你提供大量的
elemental resistances.
元素抗性。
&gt;&gt; Damn, rune of the prism is going to be
真棒，棱镜符文肯定很
nice. Wait.
厉害。 等待。
Oh, to all maximum elements. So, you
哦，致所有极致元素。 所以，你
don't want to This is early. This is
不想现在就这么做。现在还太早了。 这是
early game. You don't You don't want to
游戏初期。 我想你肯定不想在
be running this late game, I don't
游戏后期还跑这么远
think. This rune is specifically for
。 这个符文是专门为
campaign. Once you get to the end game,
战役模式设计的。 一旦到了游戏后期，
there's no way you want to be sitting at
你肯定不想
65 maximum elemental resistances,
元素抗性只有 65 点上限，
[music] which is good. This is really
[音乐] 这很好。 这真
nice. Well, this one which gives you a
不错。 嗯，这个能让你
ton of spirit.
精神振奋。
These runes are designed to be powerful,
这些符文设计之初威力强大，
but drop off in value as you level up.
但随着等级提升，其价值会逐渐下降。
They're great for power leveling a
它们非常适合快速提升
second character in the league. We also
联赛中第二个角色的等级。 我们
have six runes that can be used to
还有六种符文可以用来
expand the pool of modifiers. So, you
扩展修饰符的范围。 所以，你
got Yutyrannus Asserius, which on boots
得到了尤提拉努斯·阿塞里乌斯，这件装备的靴子
can roll chronomancy modifiers. So, like
可以附带时间魔法词缀。 比如
your cool down reduction or some sort.
减少冷却时间之类的。
Conelorn's Hunt, which on gloves can
康纳隆的狩猎，手套上可以
roll marksman modifiers. Cataclysm,
掷出神射手修正。 灾变，
which on gloves can roll decay
手套上可以随机出现衰变
modifiers. You got Medved's Tending,
词缀。 你有梅德韦德的守护，
body armors that can roll soul
可以随机生成灵魂
modifiers. Soul modifiers, interesting.
词缀的护甲。 灵魂属性修正，有意思。
Brad's Might, which on weapons can roll
布拉德之力，可以对武器进行
destruction modifiers. And Winter's
破坏性修正。 还有冬之
Grasp. We'll need to learn what the
掌控。 我们需要了解
destruction modifiers are to see if we
破坏属性修正值是多少，才能决定是否
want to roll them or not. And we'll also
要进行掷骰。 我们还会推出
have Varana's Carnage, which on helmets
瓦拉纳的屠戮，它
can roll berserking modifiers. But
可以给头盔带来狂暴修正。 但是
again, we'll need to know what the
，我们还需要知道
berserking modifiers are and also if
狂暴的修正值是什么，以及
they are going to be We'll need to know
它们是否会生效
what the berserking modifiers are. So,
。 所以，
I'm interested to see if they're going
我很想知道我们在
to have tags when we craft or how are we
制作物品时是否会有标签，或者我们如何才能
supposed to know what the berserking
知道狂暴
mods are?
词缀是什么？
Right? Are we going to have to go into
正确的？ 我们需要进入
POE 2 database for it? A little bit of
POE 2数据库吗？ 一点值得
that food for thought.
思考的内容。
&gt;&gt; So, for example, you can socket Catless
例如，你可以将“无猫之
Gloom into some gloves and it will
忧郁”镶嵌到一些手套上，这样就可以
enable the crafting of a bunch of new
制作出许多新的
decay modifiers that can be used with
衰败词缀，这些词缀可以用于
damage over time builds.
持续伤害流派。
&gt;&gt; He added a decay mod and then with the
他添加了一个衰减词缀，然后又用
exalted orb he added increased duration
崇高宝珠增加了
of damaging elements, which again, I'm
伤害元素的持续时间，但我
not sure if that is it going to be
不太确定这是否会被
labeled as a decay modifier.
标记为衰减词缀。   将
&gt;&gt; After socketing one of this type of
这种类型的
rune, use regular exalts or chaos orbs
符文镶嵌上去之后，使用普通崇高石或混沌石
to try and craft the new mods.
来尝试制作新的词缀。
&gt;&gt; With the decay rune, he rolled magnitude
他使用衰败符文，掷骰决定
of bleeding, magnitude of poison and he
流血程度、中毒程度，
was searching for damage over time
寻找持续伤害
modifiers and then he also rolled
修正，然后他还掷骰决定
increased cursed magnitudes, which is
增加诅咒程度，这很
interesting. I'm not sure if how are
有意思。 我不确定
these labeled.
这些标签是怎么标注的。
&gt;&gt; There are also several runes that have
还有一些符文会对
one-off powerful effects on items, but
物品产生一次性的强大效果，但
are bound forever into the socket.
会永远绑定在插槽中。
&gt;&gt; Wait, bound forever into the socket, so
等等，它们已经永远固定在插槽里了，所以
you can't remove them.
你无法将它们取出来。
So, once you have your rune, it won't
所以，一旦你获得了符文，
you won't be able to like overlap it
你就无法将其
with something else, which makes sense
与其他符文重叠，这很合理，
considering this one gives you a plus
因为这个符文
one suffix modifier allowed, which on
允许你获得 +1 的后缀词缀，在
gloves could be your plus two level of
手套上，它可以是 +2 等级
all, it could be attack speed, it could
，可以是攻击速度，可以
be crit damage and then leeches or
是暴击伤害，然后是吸血或其他
something to that effect.
类似效果。
&gt;&gt; Like this one, which allows any item to
例如这个，它允许任何物品
gain another suffix.
获得另一个后缀。
We slammed in Merin.
我们猛攻梅林。
Or this one, which allows you to create
或者这个，它可以让你制作
a jewel socket.
一个宝石插槽。
&gt;&gt; Destroys all augment sockets on the item
摧毁物品上的所有强化插槽，
to create a jewel socket. Now again, you
生成一个珠宝插槽。 现在，你
cannot replace that rune. It's not like
无法替换那个符文。
you can just put a regular iron rune
你不能直接在上面放一个普通的铁符文
over it. These are permanent, [music]
。 这些都是永久性的（音乐），
but it's really nice. Look at the ruby
但真的很好听。 你看
that he has on his gloves, right? Block
他手套上的红宝石，对吧？ 格挡
chance, melee damage, increased bleeding
几率、近战伤害、流血持续
duration, and gain three damage when hit
时间增加，并且受到敌人攻击时造成 3 点伤害
by an enemy. Like that's coming off of
。 就像是从
your gloves, which is really nice.
你的手套上擦掉一样，这感觉真好。
There's going to be a lot of variety of
将会有很多
different type of equipment, which is
不同类型的设备，这真的
honestly pretty exciting.
非常令人兴奋。
&gt;&gt; With this series of runes that can
这套符文可以将
convert any elemental mod from one
任何元素词缀从一种
element to another.
元素转换为另一种元素。
&gt;&gt; See these. Wrath of Aldur, martial
请看这些。 阿尔杜之怒，武术
weapon, wand or staff. When socketed it
武器，魔杖或法杖。 镶嵌后，它
transforms all fire and lightning
会将所有火焰和闪电
modifiers to equivalent cold mods. See,
词缀转换为等效的冰霜词缀。 你看，
that's going to be nice. Passion of
那会很不错。 阿尔杜尔的激情
Aldur, martial weapon, transforms all
，一件武术武器，将所有
cold and lightning mods into
冰冷和闪电MOD转化为
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; fire mods. Again, nice. Ire of Aldur,
火焰MOD。 再次称赞。 奥尔德的愤怒，
fire and cold into lightning. And
火焰与寒冷化作闪电。
betrayal of Aldur, transforms all fire,
背叛奥尔杜尔，会将物品上的所有火焰、
cold, and lightning modifiers on the
冰霜和闪电属性词缀转化
item into equivalent chaos mods.
为等值的混沌属性词缀。
&gt;&gt; There's even a rune that can upgrade any
甚至还有一种符文可以升级任何
other rune, allowing you to upgrade them
其他符文，使它们能够
beyond the normal limit.
超越正常的升级上限。
&gt;&gt; Perfect body rune.
完美体态符文。
See, this is nice. But is that a
你看，这很不错。 但这种情况会一直
permanent? She didn't say if it was
持续下去吗？ 她没有说这是否是
permanent.
永久性的。
&gt;&gt; The last one I want to show you today is
今天我要向大家展示的最后一个游戏是《
Aldur's Legacy. A special rune that can
奥尔德的遗产》。 一个特殊的符文，可以
be socketed into any Kaom's or Ezomyte
镶嵌到任何 Kaom 或 Ezomyte 上，
unique to destroy it, but creates a
以摧毁它，但会创造一个……
&gt;&gt; Okay, so this is nice. They're going to
好吧，这还不错。 他们将
make it so that we're able to identify
采取措施，使我们能够识别出可以对
which uniques we can do this on. Now,
哪些唯一对象执行此操作。 现在，
they did say with Ezomytes and Kaom's.
他们确实和 Ezomytes 和 Kaom's 说过。
Although, when they were speaking about
不过，当他们谈论
this, they were speaking about any
这件事的时候，他们指的是任何
unique, right? And now, the way he's
独特的事情，对吧？ 而现在，他只是针对这些
saying it is just the specific ones.
特定的例子来表达。
&gt;&gt; new rune that takes some of the
新的符文，继承了
properties of that unique.
该独特符文的一些特性。
So, for example, use this on a Trample
例如，在践踏脚趾符文上使用此符文，
Toe to create a Legacy of Trample Toe
即可创建践踏脚趾传承符
rune.
文。
Socket into any boots, and just like the
将其镶嵌到任何靴子上，就像
unique it came from, you'll deal 10% of
它原本的独特物品一样，你将对
overkill damage to all enemies in a 2-m
2 米半径内的所有敌人造成 10% 的超杀伤害
radius.
。
Well, how about the Legacy of Twisted
那么，《扭曲帝国的遗产》怎么样
Imperium?
？
Destroy a Twisted Imperium, and you can
摧毁一个扭曲帝国，你就可以
add cold damage based on your maximum
根据你的最大
mana to any weapon.
法力值给任何武器附加冰冷伤害。
&gt;&gt; See, that's nice. However, the way he's
你看，这挺好的。 但是，听他这么
speaking about it, it seems like it's
说，好像
get a tax with this weapon added cool
这把武器的额外
damage with that specific unique. Which
伤害（尤其是那件独特的武器）总是会额外收取一定的费用。 这
is cool, but I like the idea of it being
很棒，但我更喜欢
randomly chosen. Because then it would
随机选择的方式。 因为那样会给它
add a little bit of RNG to it.
增加一点随机性。
&gt;&gt; With Aldur's Legacy, you can create
借助《奥德的遗产》，你可以创造出大约
another hundred or so runes with all
一百个具有
sorts of unique effects.
各种独特效果的符文。
At this point, you might be thinking,
此时你可能会想，
that's a lot of new runes. And you'd be
这可是好多新符文啊。 你说得对
right. This is the runes of Aldur after
。 这毕竟是阿尔杜尔的符文
all. But we didn't want the old runes to
。 但我们也不想让古老的符文
be left behind either. A significant
被遗弃。
number of the old runes that were not
许多以前未使用的旧符文
being used have been buffed as well,
也得到了加强，
making this crafting system
使得这个制作系统变得
significantly better.
更加完善。
May 29th. See you there.
5月29日，“远古回归”更新将带你探索符文所能提供的一切。 到时见。   好了
&gt;&gt; So, there we go. These are the crafting
，就是这样。 这些是即将
runes coming and we also have those
推出的制作符文，我们还有一些
runes with the permanent buffs that
带有无法移除的永久增益效果的符文
can't be removed, which is pretty
，这非常
interesting stuff. So, let me know what
有趣。 所以，请
you guys think about that in the comment
在下面的评论区告诉我你们的想法，
section down below and also help me out
也请帮我点个
with the like, would you? Peace.
赞，好吗？ 和平。